To answer the question, willing to add the correct CSS.
للإجابة على السؤال، نريد إضافة CSS الصحيحة.
Conveniently, the class selectors have already been written out for us, so
بكل بساطة، قد تمت كتابة محددات الفئة لنا حتى الآن، لذلك
we just need to add the right properties and their values.
نريد فقط إضافة الخصائص الصحيحة وقيمها.
I'll go ahead and add those, and let's see what they do.
سأكمل وأضيفها، ولنرى ماذا تفعل.
If I save and
سأقوم بالحفظ
refresh the page, you can see that our divs now look a little bit different.
وتحديث الصفحة، يمكنك رؤية أن أقسامنا تبدو مختلفة قليلاً الآن.
The first div no longer extends from end to end on the page.
لا يمتد القسم الاول من النهاية للنهاية في الصفحة.
But instead, covers up this 100 pixel space.
لكن يغطي مساحة 100 بيكسل.
That's because we've changed the width to be 100 pixels.
هذا لأننا غيرنا العرض ليكون 100 بيكسل.
Next, the second div looks twice as tall as it used to be.
ثم يبدو القسم الثاني أطول مرتين مما كان عليه.
This makes sense because we've doubled its height from the a hundred pixels,
هذا منطقي لأن ضاعفنا ارتفاعه من 100 بيكسل،
I set it to originally.
وأعدناه إلى اصله.
Looking at the third div, we now see one of space around the div.
بالنظر إلى القسم الثالث، نري الآن 1em من المساحة حول القسم.
This comes from the use of the property margin.
وهذا نتيجة لاستخدام خاصية الهامش.
We'll cover the property margin in more detail later in this course, but
سنتحدث عن خاصية الهامش بالتفصيل لاحقًا غي هذا الدرس، لكن
try experimenting with it to see exactly what it does.
جرب استخدامها لتري بالتفصيل وظيفتها.
And finally, the paragraph in the fourth div is now using a font size
وأخيرًا، النص في القسم الرابع يستخدم حجم خط
double its previous size.
أكبر مرتين من حجمه السابق.
That's because we've set the font size to be 2em.
هذا لأننا غيرنا إعداد حجم الخط ليكون 2em.
If the font size was set to 1em, then the font size of the paragraph
إذا كان إعداد حجم الخط على 1em، سيكون حجم الخط في النص
would be exactly the same size as the paragraph in the third div.
مثل حجم الخط في القسم الثالث.
But by setting the font size to 2ems,
لكن بإعداد حجم الخط على 2ems،
we are effectively doubling its normal default size.
فإننا نضاعف حجم الخط.